Contact

0965333266 (Mobile) dth392@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ti%E1%BA %BFn-ho%C3%A0ng-%C4%91inha55803189 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Accounting Microsoft Office Report Writing

Languages

English (Professional Working) French (Professional Working) Vietnamese (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Microsoft Office Specialist: Microsoft Office Word 2013

Toeic: 985

Microsoft Office Specialist: Microsoft Office Excel 2013

Tiến Hoàng Đinh

Accountant at Vietcombank Vietnam

Summary

Being a responsible and ambitious person, I always proactively complete all assigned tasks with the highest efficiency to prove my capability and value. Besides, I am always ready to face challenges at work. With my ability to adapt and learn quickly, I am confident to overcome any obstacles on my career path. Spending time working in many companies and organizations in Vietnam and abroad has helped me to be more mature, have diverse experiences and confidence in my professional skills and know how. In the company, I am always trusted by my superiors and colleagues. By learning from my superiors and senior colleagues, I know how to work with people and promote their strengths to achieve the best result in teamwork. At the same time, I also listen to other's suggestions and criticisms in order to improve myself.

In the future, I am aiming for a position that requires high professional skills with many challenges to dedicate myself. Working in a professional and friendly environment has always been a source of motivation for me to strive and work harder. I believe that I will contribute greatly to the overall development of the organization.

Experience

Vietcombank Accountant November 2018 - Present (2 years 1 month) Hanoi, Hanoi, Vietnam

At Vietcombank, I analyze data and write monthly business reports of the branch for the Board of Directors in each briefing. Then I monitor the KPI progress of departments and staffs to pay out salaries and bonuses. Every day, I was assigned to monitor important accounts of the branch to detect erroneous entries and correct them in time ... I am also involved in negotiating foreign currency trading rate between branch and head office on demand of high-profile customers. In addition, I also participate in large project such as converting property data of the branch to synchronize with the database of the new core program. Every year, I am mobilized to check expense invoices and inventory of the branch's assets.

KARMEDIA & SPORT CO., LTD

Technical Specialist
September 2017 - May 2018 (9 months)

Hanoi, Hanoi, Vietnam

I was assigned to be treasurer and chief of technical team during the first offroad racing event in Vietnam. I have been proactively working with our French supplier ITS chrono to master the timing system and ensure its operation during the event.

Self-employed Real Estate Manager August 2017 - January 2018 (6 months) Da Nang City, Vietnam

I renovate, decorate and furnish new and old apartments then rent or sell in real estate market.

Vietnam Industry and Trade Information Centre Freelance Reporter September 2012 - October 2016 (4 years 2 months) Hanoi, Hanoi, Vietnam

I was in charge of updating daily news on bullion market for the website thongtincongthuong.vn of Vietnam Industry and Trade Information Centre which is an official department of Ministry of Industry and Trade. I always ensure the content quality and deadline for daily bulletin.

Amarris Conseil

Accountant

November 2012 - May 2014 (1 year 7 months)

Nantes, Pays de la Loire, France

I recorded accounting books and declared taxes for small and medium businesses. Before submitting their tax declaration, I reconciled accounts in balance sheet and income statement.

Banque Populaire Intern April 2012 - June 2012 (3 months) Nantes, Pays de la Loire, France I listed potential clients in the region based on their business performance and cash flow. After that, I participated in the preparation of evaluation documents before and after visiting clients.

Education

Université de Nantes Bachelor's degree, Accounting and Finance · (2010 - 2012)